{
    "questions": [{
        "id":1,
        "question": "What is Bucky's real name?",
        "option1": "Becky",
        "option2": "Dwayne",
        "option3": "Gregg",
        "option4": "Buckwheat",
        "selectedAnswer": "",
        "prevCorrectAnswered": 0,
        "correctAnswer": 3
    },{
        "id":2,
        "question":"How do you join Slack?",
        "option1":"By being lazy",
        "option2":"You have to be invited",
        "option3":"Spam Bucky",
        "option4":"Impersonate a moderator",
        "selectedAnswer":"",
        "prevCorrectAnswered":0,
        "correctAnswer":2
    },{
        "id":3,
        "question":"Who can be a programmer?",
        "option1":"A grammer professional",
        "option2":"A computer scientist",
        "option3":"Anybody",
        "option4":"A graham 'cracker'",
        "selectedAnswer":"",
        "prevCorrectAnswered":0,
        "correctAnswer":3
    },{
        "id":4,
        "question":"What is the size of Hannah's forehead?",
        "option1":"3 inches",
        "option2":"4 inches",
        "option3":"5 inches",
        "option4":"I don't know. It just makes me nervous.",
        "selectedAnswer":"",
        "prevCorrectAnswered":0,
        "correctAnswer":4
    },{
        "id":5,
        "question":"Where do you post programming questions?",
        "option1":"Bucky's wall",
        "option2":"Message Bucky",
        "option3":"The stream",
        "option4":"forum! forum! forum!",
        "selectedAnswer":"",
        "prevCorrectAnswered":0,
        "correctAnswer":4
    },{
        "id":6,
        "question":"Who is wheatley core?",
        "option1":"A bot",
        "option2":"A moderator",
        "option3":"The Ban Hammer",
        "option4":"All of the above",
        "selectedAnswer":"",
        "prevCorrectAnswered":0,
        "correctAnswer":4
    }, {
        "id":7,
        "question":"What is Bucky's room?",
        "option1":"The 'old' TNB ",
        "option2":"Bucky's bedroom",
        "option3":"A page in TNB",
        "option4":"The source code to TNB",
        "selectedAnswer":"",
        "prevCorrectAnswered":0,
        "correctAnswer":1
    },{
        "id":8,
        "question":"Who is Tiffany Alvord?",
        "option1":"A famous department store",
        "option2":"An American Idol judge",
        "option3":"Bucky's wife",
        "option4":"wheatley's girlfriend",
        "selectedAnswer":"",
        "prevCorrectAnswered":0,
        "correctAnswer":4
    },{
        "id":9,
        "question":"What is Bucky's favorite food?",
        "option1":"Bacon",
        "option2":"Tuna",
        "option3":"Hot pockets",
        "option4":"All of the above",
        "selectedAnswer":"",
        "prevCorrectAnswered":0,
        "correctAnswer":4
    },{
        "id":10,
        "question":"What is Bacon?",
        "option1":"A fruit",
        "option2":"Bacon is love! Bacon is life!",
        "option3":"A new programming language",
        "option4":"A baking product",
        "selectedAnswer":"",
        "prevCorrectAnswered":0,
        "correctAnswer":2
    }
    
    
    ]
}

